We had lost some very good men there.
我们在那里失去一些很好的弟兄
Toye and Guarnere had lost their legs there.
托伊和葛奈瑞在那里失去了腿
Guarnere... Gordon was badly hit.
戈登受到了重创
A number of other people were killed.
还有一些其他人阵亡
It was a difficult situation there.
情况非常的艰困
I don't know the exact amount of men that got killed in that...
我不知道在那里丧命兄弟的正确数目
...but six, seven of 'em, were real close friends of mine.
但是其中六七个是我最好的朋友
Skip Muck died, and Eugene Roe came to me...
史基普穆克阵亡了 而尤金罗...
...about 10 minutes after he was killed...
在他死后十分钟来找我
...and he wanted me to see if I wanted to go look at him.
问我要不要去看他
I said, no, I wouldn't be able to stand that.
而我拒绝了 我会承受不了
So, I didn't go look at him.
所以我没有去看他
After Bastogne, we went to Haguenau. There was another push there.
离开巴斯通后 我们进入哈根努 那有另一次推进
We wanted to know what was across the river there what kind of strength they had.
我们想知道 在彼岸的敌方的兵力虚实
You have a feeling you're gonna live through the war.
你感觉你会在战争中存活
You have a feeling it's starting to ease off.
你感觉战况已渐趋弛缓
You can't account for it. It's just a gut feeling.
你无法确定这只是你内心的直觉
But everybody had that feeling.
但是每个人都有这样的感觉
"I believe I might be able to live through it."
我相信我自己能活下来
So, walk carefully, take care of yourself.
所以连走路也很小心 很小心的照顾自己
The 101st Airborne had been made famous by what it did in the Battle of the Bulge.
101空降师因为突出部之役而声名大噪
Newspapers called them "the battered bastards of Bastogne."
报纸称他们是巴斯通历尽磨难的汉子
They'd been through hell...
他们经历炼狱之后
...and were now pulling into the comparative paradise of Haguenau...
现在开拔进驻相对而言像是天堂般的哈根努
...the sounds of the war still coming from just across the river.
战争的声息仍不断从仅隔一水之遥的对岸传来
I had missed Bastogne.
我错过了巴斯通之役
All I knew was what I'd read and heard around the replacement depot...
我所知道的都是在补充兵营读到和听到的
...that we had broken the enemy, and the war would soon be over.
说我们突破到敌人后方而战争很快就要结束
Thanks for the lift.
谢谢你的便车
When I was finally able to rejoin Easy Company...
当我终于能重新归回Ｅ连
...they looked nothing like the heroes who had just helped win the war.
这些人看来一点也不像刚为我们打赢一场战争的英雄
George Luz!
乔治鲁兹
Yeah?
什么事?
It's me. Come on, I haven't been gone that long.
是我 拜托 我没有离开那么久吧?
Jesus, yes, you have.
老天 是很久了
Now, look what I found.
看看我发现什么了?
Hey, guys. Sgt. Martin.
兄弟们! 马丁中士
What do you want, Private?
你要干嘛 阿兵哥?
I'm sorry, sir.
很抱歉 长官
My name's David Webster. I just got back from the hospital.
我叫大卫韦伯斯特 我刚从医院回来
Good for you.
恭喜你
Where's the rest of the guys?
其他人去哪了?
This is everybody.
全都在这里了
Come on, Sgt. Martin, this can't be everybody.
拜托 马丁中士 这怎么可能?
What about Hoobler? Where's he?
胡伯勒呢 他在哪里?
Lt. Foley, 2nd Platoon lost more guys than we did.
你知道吗 佛利少尉 第二排损失的兄弟比我们多
They're really short-handed.
他们很缺人手
Right, report to 2nd, Webster. They'll find a place for you.
对 向第二排报到 韦伯斯特 他们会帮你找个位子
Next truck up, Webster. You'll find 2nd. Move.
下一辆卡车 韦伯斯特 你会找到第二排 走吧
Hey, guys.
兄弟们
Some lieutenant told me to report to 2nd.
有位少尉叫我向第二排报到
Your name's Jackson, right?
你叫杰克森 对吗?
That's right.
没错!
Who's leading the platoon?
谁带领这一排?
Sgt. Malarkey is.
马拉其上士
What, no officers?
什么 没有军官吗?
I guess you didn't hear...
我猜你还没听说...
No, what's that?
没有 是什么?
They're making Malarkey a lieutenant.
他们将要升马拉其为军官
He's on the fast track now.
他可是快速窜升
Really? That's great.
真的? 那真好
Yeah, isn't it?
可不是吗?
Yeah. Jackson, help me up, will you?
对 杰克森 帮个忙好吗?
So, you come from the hospital?
你从医院回来的?
Yeah.
对
Must've liked that hospital, 'cause we left Holland four months ago.
你一定很喜欢那间医院 因为我们四个月前就离开荷兰了
I wasn't there the whole time.
我并没有一直待在那里
There was rehabilitation, then the replacement depot.
我还需要复原 然后到了补充兵营
I'm sure you tried to bust out and help us in Bastogne, Web.
我相信你曾试着跑回来 帮我们防守巴斯通 韦伯
I don't know how I would have done that.
我不知道怎样才能出来?
That's funny, 'cause Popeye found a way.
真有趣 因为普派做到了
So did Alley, right, back in Holland?
艾利也是 对吗? 还在荷兰的时候
And Guarnere, and...
还有葛奈瑞也...
Yeah, where is Guarnere? He still your platoon sergeant?
对 葛奈瑞在哪儿? 他还是你们排上的上士吗?
No. He got hit.
不是! 他受伤了
Yeah?
是吗?
Yeah, Bill got hit. Blew his whole leg off.
对 比尔受伤了 他整条腿被炸断
1st Platoon, moving out!
第一排 出发!
Okay, spread out.
散开来
Hold along this line till I figure out where we're going.
保持最大间距 直到我想出来下一步行动
Sarge?
中士
What's the matter, Webster?
怎么搞的 韦伯斯特?
Nervous in the service?
回来当兵会紧张吗?
No.
不会...
No, I'm fine, Sarge.
不会 我很好 中士
Why don't you go talk to Capt. Speirs. Make sure he wants you with us.
你何不去问史毕尔上尉 看他是不是要你加入我们
Capt. Speirs?
史毕尔上尉?
What happened to Capt. Winters?
温特斯上尉怎么了?
He's running the whole battalion now.
他现在是营长了
Go.
去吧
So, Easy Company had a new CO to go along with all the other new faces.
现在Ｅ连有个新的连长和一群新面孔
The guys I knew were either gone, or very different from what I remembered.
我认识的兄弟要不是不在了 就是和我记忆中不同了
I was a veteran of D-day and Market Garden...
我是Ｄ日和市场花园作战的老兵
...had been with the company since its formation...
从这个连一开始编成就参与
...but because I had missed Bastogne, I was treated as a replacement...
可是因为错过了巴斯通 我被当成补充兵对待
...and felt like I was starting all over again.
感觉像是从头来过一般
Look who it is. Nice digs, Lip?
看看这是谁? 这地方不错 李普?
- Yeah. - Sgt. Lipton?
- 对! - 李普军士长?
Hey, look what I found.
嘿 看看我找到谁了
- Feeling all right? - There you go.
- 你还好吗? - 这个给你
- He's got pneumonia. - I'm sorry to hear that.
- 他得了肺炎 - 很遗憾听到这个消息
What are you sorry about?
有什么好遗憾的?
He's alive, he's got a couch, a blanket, snug as a bug.
他还活着 他有张沙发、毛毯 像只甲虫般蜷伏着
Yeah.
对
Sgt. Malarkey said to check with the CO if I should be in 2nd Platoon.
马拉其上士说 要我跟连长确定我该待在第二排
Have a seat, Webster. We'll get you situated.
坐吧 韦伯斯特 我们会帮你安排好
How long have you been sick?
你病了多久了?
Long enough.
够久了
He wants us to cross the river.
他要我们渡过河去
Yeah, I bet that water's cold.
我打赌这河水很冷
Should be able to get you some boats.
应该会帮你弄些船来
Had to be a full moon.
今晚会是满月
So much for the cover of darkness.
想靠夜色掩护的希望不大
It's gonna leave the patrol exposed.
这样会暴露巡逻队的行动
- Is this the company CP for Easy? - Yes, sir.
- 这里是Ｅ连指挥部吗? - 是 长官
As you were.
别拘束
Lt. Jones looking for Capt. Speirs.
琼斯少尉要向史毕尔上尉报到
He's on his way, sir. Why don't you sit down?
他马上过来 长官 你要不要坐下来?
Can you get me a coffee? Would you like a coffee, sir?
能帮我倒杯咖啡吗? 你要来杯咖啡 长官?
- No, thank you. - All right.
- 不用 谢谢! - 好吧
What platoon are you in?
你是哪一排的?
We're about to find that out.
我们很快就会知道了
You got any soap? I need a shave.
你有肥皂吗 我要刮胡子
I'll send some down.
我待会拿一些过来
You know what you're doing for this?
你知道你要怎么做吗?
- I'm gonna let Speirs handle it. - Right.
- 我让史毕尔来处理 - 很好
Capt. Speirs, sir.
史毕尔上尉 长官
This is Lt. Jones.
这位是琼斯少尉
Listen, will you go back in the back and sack out?
听着 看在老天爷的份上 麻烦你回去躺好
There are beds there with fresh sheets.
那里有铺着干净床单的床铺
I will, sir.
我会的 长官
Just trying to make myself useful, sir.
只是想让我自己有些用处 长官
Listen up.
听好
Regiment wants a patrol for prisoners.
团部要出一个捕捉战俘的巡逻任务
This one comes straight from Col. Sink, so it's not my idea.
这是辛克上校的直接命令 不是我的主意
Since the river's the line of resistance, we'll cross it to get to them.
这条河是我们主要防线 所以得渡河去抓他们
What do we need to do?
我们该怎么做?
There's a three-story building on the enemy side, up the embankment.
在敌方堤岸上有座三层楼建筑
We know it's occupied.
我们知道有人驻守
You can have 15 men.
你找15人
Think very hard about who you wanna lead the patrol.
仔细想由谁来带领巡逻队
You'll need a lead scout, a translator.
你会需要一名尖兵 一名翻译员
I've got the entire battalion on covering fire.
我会要整个营作为你的掩护火力
- When? - Tonight, 0100.
- 什么时候? - 今晚1点
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Speirs, I want this one to be as fool proof, and as safe as possible.
史毕尔! 我要这次行动安全至上
Yeah, don't take any chances on this one. We're too far along for that.
对 不要冒险 我们早已不需要这么干了
Speirs, I want to discuss who might go along.
史毕尔 你想要讨论一下任务人选吗?
- Who are you? - Lt. Jones, sir.
- 你是谁? - 琼斯少尉 长官
Right, our West Pointer.
对了 我们的西点军校生
Yes, sir.
是 长官
- When did you graduate? - June 6, sir.
- 你什么时候毕业? - 六月六日 长官
June 6, of last year?
六月六日? 去年吗?
D-day, yes, sir.
D日 是 长官
All right. Don't get hurt.
很好 别受伤了
Sir, I'd like to volunteer for the patrol.
长官 我想志愿出巡逻队任务
- Speirs, talk to you in an hour. - Yeah.
- 史毕尔 一小时后见 - 是
Lt. Jones? We are short on offices.
琼斯少尉? 我们缺乏军官
You think a noncom could lead this?
你能想到一个士官担任领队吗?
I can think of a few possibilities.
我能想到三个人选
Martin, Malarkey, Grant?
马丁? 马拉其? 葛兰特?
Honestly, sir, most of the NCOs could use a rest.
老实说 长官 大部分士官都需要休息
Captain, request permission to go on the patrol.
上尉! 请求许可参加巡逻任务
There's your answer.
这是你的答案
No. You don't have any experience.
不行! 你没有任何经验
- Report to 2nd Platoon. - Yes, sir.
- 去第二排报到 - 是 长官
Tell...
告诉...
Tell Heffron, Ramirez, and McClung they're going.
告诉赫夫朗 蓝姆雷兹和麦克朗他们要去
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Sir, this is Pvt. Webster.
长官 这是上兵韦伯斯特
Sir, I'm Pvt. Webster from 1st Platoon.
长官 我是第一排的二等兵 韦伯斯特
I just got back from the hospital and Lt. Foley told me to go to 2nd...
我刚从医院回来 佛利少尉要我去第二排报到
- ...but Sgt. Malarkey said I... - Fine, 2nd.
- 可是马拉其上士说我... - 很好 第二排
Take Lt. Jones.
带着...琼斯少尉
Lieutenant, OP-2.
带少尉去第二观测所
Come on.
来吧!
Are there other officers in the platoon?
排上有其他军官吗?
No, sir. Just St. Malarkey.
没有 长官! 只有马拉其上士
But they tell me he's getting a battlefield commission.
可是他们告诉我他将获得战场委任
Maybe he'll be assisting you, sir.
也许他将辅助你 长官
Who's that?
那是谁?
Webster?
韦伯斯特?
That's right. How you doing, Sgt. Kiehn?
没错 你好吗 奇恩中士?
- Hi, Webster. - Hey, Sarge.
- 你好 韦伯斯特 - 你好 中士
Look what we just scrounged. We got some spuds.
看看我们刚找到什么? 我们有马铃薯了
Hey, OP-2, this way?
第二观测所是往这里走吗?
Shit, move! Go!
可恶 快走
Shit, they spotted us!
可恶 他们发现我们了
- Is that it? - I don't know. I think so.
- 炸完了吗? - 我不知道 也许是吧
Go, go, go!
走
Come on, come on.
快点 过来这里
All clear! All clear!
安全了! 安全了!
Okay.
好了
Wait, it was Heffron, McClung, and...
等一下 是赫夫朗、麦克朗还有...
- Ramirez, come on. - Right.
- 蓝姆雷兹 走吧! - 对
Hey, guys.
各位
- This taken? - Go ahead.
- 这床位有人睡吗? - 请便
Sergeant, this is Lt. Jones.
上士! 这位是琼斯少尉
Just assigned to 2nd Platoon.
刚被指派到第二排来
Malarkey, Platoon Sergeant.
马拉其 排上的上士
Congratulations on the battlefield commission.
恭喜你获得战地委任
The what?
获得什么?
They're making you an officer, no?
他们要将你升为军官 不是吗?
Me? No.
我? 不是
You must be thinking of First Sergeant Lipton.
你说的一定是李普军士长
My mistake.
是我听错了
So, you're without a platoon leader?
那你们没有排长了?
No, not anymore, Lieutenant.
不 不再缺了 少尉
Right.
对
So, do you wanna introduce me to the men?
你要介绍我给兄弟们认识吗?
Well, some are sleeping downstairs and the rest are right here.
有些人在楼下睡觉 其他的都在这里
Sergeant, a patrol's being planned for tonight 0100 hours, across the river.
上士 今晚1点有个渡河巡逻队的任务
Regiment wants POWs for interrogation.
团部要我们去抓几个战俘来审问
What's the situation?
现在的状况如何?
- Hey, Web. - What?
- 韦伯! - 什么事?
Come here.
过来这里
- I wanna talk to you for a second. - Why?
- 我有话跟你说 过来 - 干嘛?
- You want some coffee? - No.
- 你要咖啡吗? - 不用
- Fifteen. - Fifteen what?
- 十五 - 什么十五?
Lugies since D-day.
自从D日以来
- Any mortars? - 60s, out back.
- 有迫击炮吗? - 60炮 在后面
- Is this kid out of high school yet? - Out of West Point.
- 这小子高中毕业没有? - 他是西点军校出身
West Point? Isn't that where lke went?
西点? 那不是艾森豪威尔念的学校?
Yeah, he actually graduated with his son.
对 事实上他是和他儿子一起毕业
Shit, so...
可恶
What do you know about this patrol thing?
你对巡逻队的事知道多少?
Nothing.
我不知道
- Come on, you gotta know something. - I don't.
- 少来 韦伯你一定知道什么... - 我不知道!
Bullshit.
胡说!
You were there, right, at the CP?
你不是在指挥所?
This is a prisoner snatch, right?
这是抓俘虏的任务 对吗?
Hey, Chuck, listen to this.
恰克 你听这个
Come on, Webster, spill it.
快点 韦伯斯特 说吧
Capt. Speirs is to pick 15 men.
史毕尔上尉要挑选15个人
Lt. Jones wants to be one of them.
琼斯少尉想要参加
I say let the kid go. He could use the experience.
我建议让这孩子去 他可以得些经验
Probably could find 14 replacements to help him out.
大可找14个补充兵去帮他们
I take it this was already an outpost when you arrived?
我猜这里在你们到达时已经是个前哨站了
There were some dogies from the 79th Infantry...
来时还有几只79步兵师留下来的狗
...but they left in a hurry.
可是他们走的匆忙
What's the report on enemy activity?
敌军动态报告如何?
Expect some flares, a few mortars at night...
在夜间会有些照明弹和迫击炮
...scattered 88s, snipers during the day.
零星的88毫米炮 白天有狙击手
Yeah, we dodged some mortars on our way in.
对 我们在来的路上躲了几发迫炮
They also got some sort of railroad gun back there.
他们那边还有铁路大炮
Shells about the size of a deuce and a half.
炮弹有两吨半小卡车那么大
Sounds like a freight train when one comes over.
经过时听起来像是货运列车
They haven't attempted to cross the river?
可是他们没有企图渡河?
No.
没有
They have roofs over their heads, sir. Just like us.
他们头上有屋顶掩蔽 跟我们一样
I don't think anybody wants to do anything stupid at this point, right?
我想这个时候没有人想要轻举妄动
Why are you holding out? I know you know.
你为什么想瞒着我? 我知道你知道的
- Just give us the names, Web. - Who?
- 跟我们说有谁就好了 韦伯 - 有谁?
There are three men here in this room, that think they should be on the patrol.
在这屋里有三个人 是他们认为要出巡逻任务的
Who?
谁?
If I tell you, you can't let on that you know.
如果我告诉你们 可不能说你们已经知道了
Your secret's safe, Web. Who is it?
放心 韦伯 到底是谁?
Yeah, Heffron.
赫夫朗
Shit!
可恶
McClung.
麦克朗
And you.
还有你
He want any other guys from any other platoon?
他要其他排的人参与吗?
No, I don't know. Not that I know of.
我不知道 据我所知没有
Look, that's all I know, I'm sorry.
我知道的就是这些了 很抱歉
So, it's McClung, Heffron, and Ramirez.
所以是麦克朗 赫夫朗还有蓝姆雷兹?
- I'll tell them. I just need you to point... - Listen up!
- 我会告诉他们 你只要... - 注意!
Got some bad news.
我有坏消息...
There is a patrol set for tonight, and so far, Speirs wants McClung...
今晚有个巡逻任务 目前为止 史毕尔要麦克朗...
- We know. - Yeah, we just fucking heard.
- 我们知道了 - 我们刚听说了
Webster here told us.
韦伯斯特告诉我们了
Easy, White.
Ｅ连白
Yeah.
对
Okay. All right, out.
好 完毕
The PX rations just came in.
Px级补给刚到
Including winter shoe pacs.
包括冬季鞋具
- Beautiful. - Yeah, finally, right?
- 棒极了! - 对 终于...
Good of 'em. Now we're in a nice warm house.
他们真好! 现在这是间温暖的好房子了
Also, we get showers.
还有 我们可以淋浴了
All right, let's move! Clear it out!
我们快走 离开这里
Come on, move, move!
老天 走...!
Incoming!
敌炮射击
Come on, come on, go!
快走...
Stay down! Stay low, stay low!
蹲下!
Okay.
好了
Showers, let's go, come on.
淋浴去 我们走吧
Somebody's been hit!
有人中弹了
- What happened? - Casualty.
- 发生什么事? - 有人阵亡
- Who is it? - Bill Kiehn.
- 是谁? - 比尔奇恩
I just left him. I was on my way back.
我刚与他分手 我在回来路上遇到他
In war, soldiers sometimes die in the fever pitch of a firefight...
在战时 士兵有时会因努力救火
...or by artillery when they're huddled in a foxhole.
或是炮击而死在散兵坑里
Bill Kiehn, a Toccoa man...
比尔奇恩 塔可亚基地的老兵
...was killed because he was carrying potatoes from one building into another...
因背着一袋马铃薯...从一栋建筑走到另一栋而丧命
...in the wrong place at the wrong time.
地点与时机却都不对
He was dead before Doc Roe even heard the call for a medic.
他在罗医生被召来之前就断气了
Get him out of here, will you?
把他抬走 好吗?
- Let's go, let's get out of here. - Yeah, okay.
- 我们走吧 离开这里 - 好吧
Did you know him well?
你跟他熟吗?
No, not really.
不太熟
McClung.
麦克朗
Thanks.
谢谢
Malarkey.
马拉其
Jackson, you and Liebgott, Powers, Wynn, and Webster.
杰克森 你还有李高特 鲍尔斯 怀恩及韦伯斯特
All right?
好吗?
2nd Platoon, on me.
第二排 来我这里
All right, I'm leading this patrol.
我带领这次的巡逻任务
CO wants Grant, Liebgott, Wynn...
上尉要葛兰特 李高特 怀恩...
...Jackson, Shifty from 3rd Platoon, and Webster.
杰克森 第三排的西福弟以及韦伯斯特
- They want anyone from 1st? - No.
- 他们有叫第一排的人吗? - 没有
- Anyone they don't want from 2nd? - Jesus Christ.
- 第二排有他们没点到的吗? - 天啊
That list sounds like everybody to me.
从名单上看 都是我们的人
It's always 2nd Platoon.
总是二排
Swear to God, if we had three guys, they'd still want us for it.
我发誓如果我们只剩三个人 他们还会让我们去的
I can't believe Malarkey's gonna lead it.
我不敢相信 他们要马拉其带队
He only lost his five best friends. What the fuck's he gotta live for?
他只失去他五位好友 他还有什么好值得活的
Has it been a long time since your last shower, Professor?
你上回淋浴到现在很久了吧 教授?
- Come on. - Is it hot water or cold?
- 来吧! - 是热水还是冷水?
- Come on, hurry up, will ya? - All right.
- 过来 快点 - 好的
I guess I don't really need a shower.
我想我不需要淋浴
I don't either.
我也不需要
- Lieutenant? - Yeah.
- 少尉? - 什么事?
- You still wanna get your ODs dirty? - Of course.
- 你还是想出这趟任务吗? - 当然!
I was just thinking.
我刚在想
Sgt. Malarkey's really in no condition to be on this patrol.
马拉其上士的状况真的不适合出任务
And maybe, if you offered, you could go in his place.
也许你主动向他提你可以取代他的位置
- Being that you are an officer... - No, they want someone with experience.
- 毕竟你是位军官... - 不行 他们要有经验的人
The guys they picked have plenty of that.
他们选的兄弟们都经验老到
Lt. Jones wanted to experience combat before the war was over.
琼斯少尉想在战争结束之前 亲身体验战斗
Malarkey had been on the front lines every time Easy Company had seen action since D-day.
唐马拉其从D日后 Ｅ连的每场战役他都身处前线
If it was possible for them to switch places for the patrol...
如果有可能让他们在这次巡逻任务对调
...it would be a small moment of justice.
这样安排会稍微公平一点
As welcome as a hot shower and a fresh uniform.
就像热水澡跟干净制服一样受弟兄们欢迎
The decision, though, was not theirs to make.
然而这却不是他俩能够私下决定的
Goddamn it, Johnny, you're breaking my heart, I'm telling you.
可恶 强尼 我告诉你 你伤透了我的心
Come on, George, just give me, I don't know, 10, 15 bars.
拜托 乔治 你就给我...十...十五条
Juicy Fruit. Happy?
水果糖 高兴了吗?
We just got a report of movement.
我们刚收到敌军动态报告
Lipton wants you to lay a few bazooka rounds into a house across the river.
李普军士长要你向河对岸一栋房子发射几发火箭弹
You'd think we could get at least one Hershey bar.
你想我们能拿到至少一条贺喜巧克力棒
You're 1st Platoon at heart.
你心里是第一排的
Jesus, Cobb, there's not enough.
卡伯 这样不够
Hershey bars!
贺喜巧克力棒
Jesus Christ.
天
- Wait your turn. - Who are they for?
- 排队等 - 这些是要给谁的?
- Not you, Lieb. - Come on, George, one bar.
- 不是给你的 李 - 乔治 给我一条
- No, there's not enough to go around. - Capt. Speirs here?
- 不可以 这些不够给每个人 - 史毕尔上尉在吗?
Down by the river, sir.
在河边 长官
Hey, big mouth, give the kid a Hershey bar.
大嘴 给孩子们一条贺喜棒 如何?
You gotta be shittin' me!
这怎么可能?
What's up, guys?
大家好吗?
- I like what you did with the place, George. - Yeah, I did good.
- 我喜欢这里的布置 乔治 - 对...弄得不错
- How you feeling? - If you keep your hands off my ass, fine.
- 你感觉如何? - 只要你们别碰我的屁股就没事
- Have a Hershey. - Thanks.
- 来个巧克力 - 谢谢
- He gets a fuckin' Hershey bar? - He got shot in the ass.
- 他就有巧克力吃? - 他屁股中弹
Did I tell you to stick your ass out in the wind?
我有叫你把大屁股在寒风里翘得很高吗?
No, but I expect a little sympathy from you, right?
没有 可是我期待你们给我一点同情
I should rub it for you?
你要我来帮你揉揉吗?
Can you believe this guy?
你们相信吗?
Try to get him out of the war, he comes back.
想办法要他离开 他又跑回来
That's not what I heard. I heard the Krauts are finished.
这不是我听到的 我听说德军战败了
Yeah, just to make sure...
对 为了确定起见
...we've gotta row across the fucking river tonight...
我们今晚要划过河
...grab a few, and ask 'em in person.
去抓几个德军 亲自问他们
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑?
Wish I was. Welcome back, Frank.
我希望我是 欢迎归队 法兰克
Yeah, Jesus, that reminds me, Web, I need you to run these to OP-2 for me.
这提醒了我 韦伯 我要你拿这给第二观测所
Grenade launchers for the night patrol.
晚上巡逻队要用的枪榴弹发射器
Any day now, Web, there you go.
随时会用到 韦伯 拿去
You know what? Send these, too.
这样吧 把这也拿去
Did you hear what happened on D-company's patrol last night?
你们有听说昨晚Ｄ连出的巡逻任务吗?
- What? - Replacement lieutenant blew his foot off.
- 怎样? - 新来的少尉把脚给炸断了
Stepped on a Schu mine. Fresh in from West Point.
踩到德军地雷 才刚从西点军校毕业
Had to come back empty handed.
就得两手空空的回去
No shit.
真的
- Maybe he's a friend of yours, Lieutenant. - What you got in there?
- 说不定是你的朋友 少尉 - 你那里还有些什么?
More Hershey bars and Lucky Strikes for you rear-echelon fucks to hoard?
更多巧克力和香烟 被你们这些低阶菜鸟藏起来了?
Cobb, with the mouth, please. The kid's just trying to do his job, all right?
别这样 卡伯 把嘴巴闭上 这孩子只在乎他的工作
Jesus Christ. You know what? To hell with it.
我的老天 你知道吗? 我真是懒得理你们了
Count 'em up, Vest. I gotta go blast this house.
把它们算一算 魏斯特 我得去把这房子给炸了
- You happy now? - You coming, Perco?
- 你现在高兴了吧? - 你要一起来吗 派康提?
Make yourself useful, watch this shit for me.
让你有点事做 你帮我看好这里
Web, you're coming with me.
韦伯 你跟我去
Is Capt. Speirs gonna be where you're headed?
上士 史毕尔上尉会在你去的地方吗?
- Same vicinity, yeah. - Then I'll join you.
- 差不多在附近 - 好 那我跟着你走
- Where are we going? - To the house I gotta blast.
- 你要去哪里? - 去我要炸的房子
Capt. Winters gonna be with him?
温特斯上尉会见他吗?
Jesus, look, I don't know, maybe.
我不知道 也许吧
- Then I'm coming, too. - All right, come on, please.
- 那我也去 - 好了 一个个来
Take it easy, I've been here all fucking day. Give me a bar.
快点 我等好久了 给我一根巧克力
Come on, you don't even smoke cigarettes, damn it!
拜托 你又不抽烟
Come on, I got a wounded ass.
拜托 我屁股受伤
Did intelligence give you any information on the CP?
指挥部的情报单位有没有给你任何讯息?
Third house on the left.
左边第三栋房子
Soon as our men are in the boats, I want a quad 50 opening up.
我们的人一到船上 就要用火力控制
Capt. Winters?
温特斯上尉
About the patrol.
有关这次巡逻任务
I feel that I should go on the patrol, sir. I know I could use the experience.
我觉得我应该去 长官 我知道我能吸取经验
Denied. Anything else?
请求拒绝! 还有事吗?
You're not gonna lead that patrol, Lt. Jones.
不可能让你带领巡逻队 琼斯少尉
Permission to speak, sir.
请求发言 长官
Go on, Lieutenant.
说吧 少尉
It looks like Sgt. Malarkey could use a break.
马拉其上士可能需要休息 长官
I've discussed it with him, he said he didn't mind if I took his place on the patrol.
我已经跟他谈过 他不介意我替他出巡逻任务
That was nice of him.
他真是好心
- Capt. Winters. - Yes.
- 温特斯上尉 - 什么事?
I'd really like to be on that patrol, sir.
我真的很想参加巡逻队 长官
If it's true the Krauts are finished...
如果德军真的要垮了
I haven't really done anything except deliver mail and type morning reports.
那我除了送信跟打报告外没有真正做过任何事
Absolutely.
没问题
Thank you, Captain.
谢谢你 上尉
He's got a point about Sgt. Malarkey.
他对马拉其的说法有些道理
Yeah, a point.
是 有点道理
Fine, you can go.
好吧 你可以去
There'll be a briefing, CP, 1700.
在指挥部17时会有简报
Yes, sir.
是 长官
So, who do you have in mind leading this thing, if not Malarkey?
如果不是马拉其 你想要谁来带队?
Come on. He can't be leading.
拜托 他不可能带队
I'm not sure what they decided.
我不确定他们的决定原因
No way. Not on his first day.
不行 不能在他的第一天
Do you see any other officer here?
你看到其他军官在这里吗?
What?
什么?
They call you guys, too?
他们也有叫你吗?
So, who's in charge of this bullshit?
是谁负责这次狗屎行动?
No, he ain't.
不会是他
If he ain't, it's you, Chuck. Or Shifty or Mo.
如果不是他 就是你了 恰克 西福第或者是莫
That'd be better.
这样还比较好
Ten-hutt!
立正!
At ease.
稍息
- Gentlemen. - Sir.
- 各位 - 长官
As you can see, we've assembled 15 of you here for this prisoner snatch tonight, 0100.
如你们所见 我们已为今晚1点的行动召集了15人
Just a couple of points.
几点要注意的
Secured four rubber boats to get you across the river.
我们已经取得四艘橡皮艇让你们能渡过河
Lt. Jones here is the ranking officer...
琼斯少尉是最高阶长官
...and he'll be along as an observer.
他会以观察员的身份跟着过去
Sgt. Martin here will lead the patrol in Sgt. Malarkey's place.
马丁中士将代替马拉其上士带领巡逻队
The whole battalion will be covering your withdrawal.
全营将会掩护你们的撤退
We've identified targets. We've planned fire for 'em.
我们已经确认了目标 也计划好对它的火力攻击
We hear these whistles, we open up.
我们一听到这个哨音 我们就开火射击
So don't blow them till you're back in the boats with your prisoners.
所以在你们带着俘虏回到船上前不要吹它
If the house turns out to be empty, sir?
如果房子是空的呢 长官
It won't, but in any case...
不会的! 万一是空的
...we know it's an outpost, we want it destroyed...
我们也知道它是一栋观测站 需要将它摧毁
...so you have to lay some demo on a time delay.
所以你们要装设定时炸药
You have to move fast, but carefully. Put a perimeter around the house.
你们要快速但小心地移动 将房子四周围住
Once in place, get rifle grenades in the window.
布置完毕后 将枪榴弹射进一楼窗户
Get your assault team in quick. Okay, good, understood.
接着突击队快速进入 好 明白吧
Remember, it's about prisoners.
记得 这次是要抓俘虏
Don't pop the first thing that moves.
别看到会动的就开枪
- Clear? - Yes, sir.
- 清楚了吗? - 清楚了 长官
Good.
很好
Picked your assault team?
挑选突击小组
McClung, Sisk, Cobb, Garcia...
麦克朗 西斯克 卡伯 贾西亚
...and Webster, as translator.
还有韦伯斯特充当翻译员
The rest of you guys, a base of fire with Sgt. Grant.
其余的人跟着葛兰特中士担任基本火力
You speak German, right, Webster?
你会说德语? 对吧 韦伯斯特?
Yeah, a little bit.
对 会讲一点
Good.
很好
That's my team, sir.
这就是我的小组 长官
Questions?
有问题吗?
No, sir.
没有 长官
Good.
很好
Good luck.
祝好运
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你 长官
Ten-hutt!
立正
As you were. Carry on.
继续 好好努力
A little German?
一点点德语?
His German's as good as mine.
他的德语跟我一样好
It's not a concern of mine. - Jackson, you need this.
- 嘿 杰克森 这个给你 你用得着 - 谢谢!
Can you believe that guy?
我真不敢相信那个家伙
Webster, likes to get out of everything.
韦伯斯特 什么事他都想要逃避
Whatever.
管他的
I want four men on each block.
我在每条街之间要四个人
Four men to go in.
四个人攻进去
Four on the left flank, four on the right.
四人在左翼 四人在右
- Sir? - Yes?
- 长官 - 什么事?
- Liebgott and I, we both speak German. - Yeah?
- 李高特跟我都会说德语 - 所以呢?
You said 15 men, there are 16 of us, including two translators.
你说15个人 现在有16个 包括两位翻译员
Fine. Liebgott, you wanna sit this one out?
很好 李高特 你这次不去如何
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Martin, you wanna supervise the street squads?
马丁 你要管理三个班?
- Thank you, sir. - Or the two fives?
- 谢谢你 长官 - 好了 我去 我当然去
Yeah, anyway...
好
Okay, you men going on patrol...
好 参加巡逻任务的人
...Skinny, nothing rattles, nothing shines, no helmets.
史基尼 别带会响的 会反光的 不要戴头盔
Lieutenant?
少尉
Thank you.
谢谢
Are you set for tonight?
你为今晚准备好了吗?
I'm ready.
我准备好了
- Those Krauts are gonna catch some hell. - So I hear.
- 那群德国佬要倒霉了 - 我听说了
I'm not personally going in.
我本人不进去
It's Martin, right?
是马丁 对吗?
Martin and McClung.
对 马丁跟麦克朗
I'm supposed to stay in the rear and give them cover.
我要留在后方替他们掩护
It's the best place to be.
那是最好的位置
Fifteen men crossing a river to capture prisoners from a German observation post.
十五个人过河到一个德国观察点去抓战俘
Getting back safely could be successfully accomplished in as little as ten minutes.
要安全的回来 最快十分钟内就可以完成
The same mission could be met with disaster...
这样的任务也可能会是场灾难
...and result in nothing more than 15 Americans killed or wounded in action.
除了导致死伤15位美国人外 一无所获
Those of us who had seen combat before put that out of our minds.
我们之中经历过战斗的 把这些抛到脑后
Those who hadn't probably thought of little else as we waited for darkness.
那些想得比我们不见得少的人 在等待着天黑
- Any problems? - No problems.
- 有问题吗? - 没问题
It's secured to the tree. No sign of any AP mines.
绳子已经绑牢了 没有发现地雷
Let's go.
我们走
Webster, come on.
韦伯斯特 快点
Keep it steady.
稳住
Shit.
可恶
- I can't swim! - Garcia, grab Sisk.
- 我不会游泳! - 贾西亚 去救西斯克
Okay, keep going, come on. Stay focused. Come on.
继续往前 快点 集中精神
Use the rope.
用绳子
Come on.
快点
Cutters.
破坏剪
Good.
很好
To the side.
卷到旁边
Let's go, come on.
我们走 快来
Clear.
安全了
Easy now, clear.
轻一点 安全了
Powers, go. Go, McClung.
鲍尔斯 上 麦克朗 上
McClung, move up.
麦克朗 前进
In twos, up.
两个两个 上
Powers, Wynn, secure the left flank.
鲍尔斯 怀恩 守住左翼
Lieutenant...
少尉
...take Grant and Heffron secure the right perimeter and crossroads.
带着葛兰特跟赫夫朗...守住右侧周边及交叉路口
Clear?
清楚吗?
Security out, go. Move.
警戒兵出发 走
Come on, let's go.
我们走
Jackson, hold on!
杰克森 等一下
Put it down!
把枪放下
Put it down, and keep your hands out where I can see them!
把枪放下 把手举到我看得到的地方
Keep those Krauts quiet!
叫这些德国佬安静
Jackson!
杰克森
Vest, take care of him.
魏斯特 你照顾他
Ramirez, watch Vest.
蓝姆雷兹 你守着魏斯特
Let's go, Webster, let's go.
我们走 韦伯斯特 我们走
Split 'em up, come on.
押好他们 快点
Webster, check 'em for weapons.
韦伯斯特 搜他们的武器
Keep those men quiet!
叫他们安静
McClung, cover 'em!
麦克朗 掩护他们
Take the charges, prime it, bury it.
韦伯斯特 拿炸药来 装好 理进去
Shut up, you two, and pick him up.
你们两个闭嘴 把他扶起来
McClung, these two are gonna carry the wounded Kraut.
麦克朗 这两个要扛受伤的德军
Tell 'em. Bring the wounded man.
告诉他们 带受伤的来
I said, shut up.
我叫你们闭嘴!
Ramirez, pick up Jackson! We're moving out!
蓝姆雷兹你扶杰克森 我们要走了
Come on, where are you going? You, move!
快点 你要去哪里?
Everybody moves out on my command.
每个人听我命令离开
Are you ready? Are you ready?
你们准备好了吗?
Shut up, you! Come on, we all go together.
你闭嘴! 快点 我们要一起走
Let's go, move, move out! Let's go, move! Move!
我们走 走!
Webster, come on!
韦伯斯特 快点
Powers, fall back, we're moving out!
鲍尔斯 撤退! 我们要离开了!
Keep those prisoners' heads down, and let's keep moving.
麦克朗 把俘虏头压低 我们继续撤退
Wynn! Fall back! We're moving out, let's go.
怀恩 撤退 我们要离开了! 我们走!
We're falling back! Covering fire!
我们要撤了 掩护射击!
Heffron, I want you to fall back now! Let's go!
赫夫朗 我要你马上撤退! 我们走了!
Move out, get back to the boat, I'll cover.
撤退! 回船上去 我来掩护
Go!
快走!
Keep those men moving!
要他们快走!
Lieutenant, take the whistle. Let's go!
少尉 拿着哨子 我们走!
Go!
快走!
Let's go!
我们快走!
Stay low, keep moving!
姿势放低 快走
Fall back to the boats, now! Fall back!
快走 撤回船上 快! 撤退
Jesus Christ, come on, blow the goddamn whistle!
快点 快点吹哨
Okay, everybody, get in the boats, right now!
好 大家快上船 马上
Come on, get in the boats.
快上船 快走
Come on, move! Let's go, Shifty. I'm gonna shoot you, you fucking Kraut!
快 西福弟 我要把你给宰了 臭德国佬
Shoot him, we'll have to come back for more.
你杀了他 我们还得再回来抓别人
You, in the boat, now! You get up, you Kraut piece of shit!
你 马上上船 站起来 你这个臭德国佬
Into the boats! Quick, get in the boats, come on!
上船 快点
Let's go, we're moving out!
走 我们要离开了
Let's get these boats in the water!
大家把船放到水里
Let's do it, start pulling.
一起来 开始拉
You're okay, Jackson!
你没事的 杰克森
Keep pulling!
继续拉
Come on, keep going, come on!
快 继续前进 快
Perconte, come on, let's go!
派康提 快点 我们走!
Where's the medic?
医护兵在哪里?
Everybody off the boats! Let's go!
大家快下船 我们走
Take cover!
找掩体
We got wounded, come on.
我们有人受伤了 快点
Popeye, get the Krauts back there, and shake 'em down.
普派 把德国佬带过来 把他们搜一遍
Move! Move!
快走
McClung, McClung!
麦克朗中士
Get onto the company CP! Let 'em know what we got!
接连指挥部 告诉他们我们的战果
Shut up, just shut up.
闭嘴 给我闭嘴
I can't do this, I can't do this.
我做不到
Move off. Webster, stay with him.
走开! 韦伯斯特 你陪着他
Hey, Shifty, watch Vest.
西福弟! 看着魏斯特
Sir, I'm going to get a medic.
长官 我要去找医护兵来
- You got this? - Yeah.
- 你能处理吗? - 可以
- Get his legs. - Jackson, listen to me.
- 抓住他的脚 - 杰克森 听我说
Calm down, or we can't help you.
你要冷静 不然我们设法帮你
Settle down.
静下来
He's gonna fucking die!
他都他妈的快死啦!
Jackson, look at me, don't listen to him.
杰克森 看着我 别听他的
Look at me. You're gonna be fine. Everything's gonna be okay.
看着我 你会没事的 一切都会好的
Keep still. Be calm, buddy, everything's fine. Everything's fine.
不要动 保持冷静 会没事的
Goddamn it!
可恶!
Jesus!
老天!
You think you're out of this war? What do you think you're doing?
你以为你摆脱了这场战争? 想清楚你到底在干什么?
We're not gonna get more prisoners, because you killed one!
我们不想因为你杀了俘虏还得再来一遍
Private, listen to me, Private. He's gonna fucking die!
听我说 阿兵哥 他都他妈的快死啦!
Sit down! Jackson, stay calm, the medic is coming.
坐下! 杰克森 保持冷静 医护兵这就来
- They're on their way. - Where the fuck is the medic?
- 他们这就来 - 医护兵他妈的在哪?
Doc is on his way.
医生在路上
- You'll be okay. All right, - Jackson, you got the doc.
- 你会好的...好 - 杰克森 医生到了
- Doc's here, you're okay. - All right, Jackson, take it easy, okay.
- 医生在这 没事了 - 好了 杰克森 放松
Okay.
没事
Light, I need some light, give me some light.
光 我需要光线 帮我照亮一点
All right, look at the flame, Jackson.
杰克森 看着火焰
Okay, that's good.
好 很好
All right, let's get him out of here.
好 把他抬走
You guys, help the doc move him.
你们帮医生把他抬起来
I don't wanna die, I don't wanna die!
我不想死...
- It's okay, Jackson. - I don't wanna die!
- 没事的 杰克森 - 我不想死...
Take it easy.
放松
It's okay, it's okay.
没事的
You're all right. Jackson!
你会好的 杰克森
- God, my God! - Jackson, you're not gonna die.
- 天啊 我的天! - 杰克森 你不会死的
You're not gonna die, I need you to hang on!
你不会死的 你要撑下去
Jackson!
杰克森!
Eugene Jackson was 20 years old.
尤金·杰克森当时才20岁
He'd lied about his age when he joined the army at 16.
他16岁时谎报年龄加入了陆军
His family, I'm sure, got a telegram...
我相信他的家人收到...
...from the War Department, saying he died a hero...
战争部发的电报 说他是在...
...on an important mission that would help win the war.
一场关键性战役中英勇牺性
In fact, Eugene lost his life on a stretcher in a dank basement in Haguenau...
事实上 尤金是在哈根努一间潮湿地下室的担架上
...crying out in agony while his friends looked on helplessly.
在他朋友们无助的看着他痛苦地嘶喊而去世
He was just one more casualty in a war that was supposed to be all but over.
他只是这场无尽战事中又一位牺牲者
Did they put that in the report on the ADA?
他们有没有把这点写到战事报告里去?
We're working on it. How long are you gonna keep...
我们正在办 你还要留着部队多久
Keep moving, go on.
走
Get up on the truck.
上卡车
Up, up.
上去
Status?
状况如何?
Private Jackson took a grenade fragment from the enemy OP.
一等兵杰克森在敌军观测所被手榴弹弹片击中
It was his own grenade.
那是他自己的手榴弹
He died of his wounds, sir.
他伤重不治 长官
Any others?
还有别人吗?
No, sir.
没有了 长官
Well executed.
任务达成
It's not your fault.
不是你的错
Talk to your men.
跟兄弟们谈谈
- Carry on. - Thank you, sir.
- 继续努力 - 走吧 谢谢你 长官
We heard you got two prisoners.
听说你们抓到两名俘虏
Good work.
干得好
Jackson's dead.
杰克森死了
Yeah, we heard.
对 我们听说了
They want another patrol tonight.
他们今晚还要再派巡逻任务
What are you doing, Cobb?
你在干什么 卡伯?
You leave someone on the bank?
你们有留人在河岸上?
Yeah, yeah, we did.
对 我们有
It's the third prisoner that was too far-gone to bring back.
那是第三名战俘 伤得太重 我们带不回来
Maybe we should put him out of his misery.
也许我们该给他一枪 结束他的痛苦
Fuck his misery.
管他多痛苦
I can't listen to it anymore.
我听不下去了
- Sir, want cigarette? - Yeah.
- 长官 抽烟吗? - 好的
Who's got a light?
谁有火?
Here, sir.
我有 长官
Twenty-two.
二十二
What you looking at, Webster?
你看什么看 韦伯斯特
Yeah, that's what I thought, college boy.
怎样? 我也是这么想的 大学生
Are you drunk, trooper?
你醉了吗 阿兵哥?
Leave me alone.
不要管我
Answer the question.
回答我的问题
Yes, sir, I am drunk, sir.
是 长官 我是醉了
Drunk.
醉了
Sick and tired of fucking patrols, taking orders...
厌倦了这个鬼巡逻 厌倦接受指令
Hey, Cobb, shut up. It's boring, okay?
卡伯! 闭嘴! 说这个很无聊
Taking his side, Johnny?
帮他说吗 强尼?
Yeah...I am.
对! 我是
- So, he knows we lost a man? - Yeah, he knows.
- 他知道我们损失了一名兄弟? - 对 他知道
He also knows you picked up two prisoners who talked.
他也知道你捉到了两名会说口供的俘虏
About what?
关于什么?
OB, supply trouble, Hitler's favorite color.
OB 就是补给的问题 还有希特勒最喜欢的颜色
I don't know. None of it gets us across the river.
我不知道 这些都没办法帮我们渡过河去
What's the point?
你要说明什么?
Honestly?
说实话吗?
Sink's been on the phone all day, bragging it up.
辛克整天都在讲电话 大吹大擂
I think he's just showing off now.
我想他现在只是在炫耀
I don't know, Dick. I don't know what to tell you.
我不知道 迪克 我不知道要告诉你什么
You gave him a successful patrol, now he wants two.
你给了他一个成功的巡逻 他现在还想再要一个
Successful.
成功
Sir, the men are mustered.
长官 兄弟们都集合好了
If you want me to brief 'em, I'm gonna.
如果你要我给他们简报 我马上去
It's the same roster as last night.
队员名单跟昨晚一样
Well, mostly.
几乎一样
- Evening, gents. - Evening, Colonel.
- 晚上好 各位 - 晚上好 上校
At ease.
稍息
Y'all did a damn fine job on a tough mission last night.
你们昨晚成功的执行了一次艰难的任务
And I wish you good luck tonight, 'cause I'll be expecting more of the same.
我祝你们今晚好运 因为我期待有更多的收获
- Have you briefed the men? - Just on our way, sir.
- 你们给兄弟们简报了吗? - 正要去 长官
All right.
很好
Make damn sure you remind 'em how proud I am of what they did.
记得要告诉他们 我对他们的表现感到骄傲
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
So, I'll brief 'em now, sir?
那我现在去给他们简报 长官?
No.
不...
No, I'll do it.
不...由我来
Sarge, they're on their way in.
中士 他们来了
Ten-hutt.
立正!
- Martin. - Sir.
- 马丁 - 长官
At ease.
稍息
- This everybody, Grant? - Sir.
- 大家都到了吗 葛兰特? - 是 长官
You men did an excellent job last night.
你们昨晚干得很好
I...
我...
I'm proud.
我很自豪!
I just saw Col. Sink. He's proud, too.
我刚遇到辛克上校 他也很自豪
In fact, he's so proud, he wants you to do another patrol across the river tonight.
自豪得要你们今晚再次过河执行任务
Any moment now, the outpost we hit last night...
我们昨晚进攻的观测所...
- ...will go up in flames, Martin? - Yes, sir.
- 是不是随时都可能爆炸 马丁? - 是 长官
It means we'd have to venture farther into town this time.
表示这次得冒险更深入城里
- Capt. Speirs, you have the map, please? - Yeah, Sgt. Grant.
- 史毕尔上尉 你拿地图 - 是 葛兰特中士
We have enemy movement here and here...
在这有敌军活动 还有这里...
...which means this is our new house target here.
表示我们的新目标建筑在此
We recovered all the boats so we'll set off from the same place as last night.
我们找回了所有船只 出发地点跟昨晚相同
We're not changing the plan any, sir?
我们的计划都没有改变吗 长官?
No. Plan is the same.
没有! 计划是一样的
It will be 0200 hours instead of 0100.
只是时间改成2点而不是1点
- Is that clear? - Yes, sir.
- 清楚吗? - 是 长官
Okay. Good, because...
很好 因为
...I want you all to get a full night's sleep tonight.
我要你们大家今晚好好睡一觉
Which means, in the morning you will report to me that you made it across the river...
也就是说 明天早上来跟我报告说 你们渡过了河
...into German lines...
进入德军防线
...but were unable to secure any live prisoners.
可是没办法活捉任何的德军俘虏
Understand?
懂吗?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Good.
很好
Look sharp for tomorrow.
明天要看起来有精神
We're moving off the line.
我们要从防线撤离了
- Did I fucking hear that right? - A good man.
- 我没听错吧? - 他真是个好人
Moving off the line.
撤离防线
It's a whole new way to fight a war.
这是个全新的作战方法
Don't bother writing this up. I'll take care of it.
你报告甭写了 我会搞定
- I might actually enjoy it. - Okay.
- 我也许会写得很高兴 - 好的
Think you might be onto something, Dick.
我就知道你在盘算些什么 迪克
- Lt. Jones. - Sir.
- 琼斯少尉 - 长官
Join us at the company CP.
跟我们去连指挥部
- First Sergeant Lipton. - Sir.
- 李普军士长 - 长官
Your honorable discharge as an enlisted man.
你的士兵身分光荣解除了
Just keep 'em coming, Luz.
继续拿过来 鲁兹
Battlefield commission as Second Lieutenant.
这是你的少尉军官战场委任令
- Look what we have here, boys. - Hey, pal.
- 看看这里是谁? - 嘿
- Congratulations, Carwood. - Thank you, sir.
- 恭喜你 卡伍德 - 谢谢你 长官
- Lip, congratulations. - Thanks.
- 李普 恭喜! - 谢谢!
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, welcome back, sir.
- 谢谢你 长官 - 谢谢你! 欢迎回来 长官
- That's Harry to you. Congratulations. - Thanks, Harry.
- 你该改叫我哈利了 恭喜! - 谢谢你 哈利
Harry, I didn't expect to see you this soon.
哈利 我没想到那么快就见到你
I figured you'd be nursing that scratch for another month or two.
我以为你还得照顾你那个擦伤一两个月
Did you miss me, Lewis?
你想念我吗? 路易斯?
Lt. Jones.
琼斯少尉
Regiment has seen fit to promote you to First Lieutenant.
团部认为你合格升中尉了
They want you on staff up there.
他们希望你更上一层楼
- Congratulations and good luck. - Thank you, sir.
- 恭喜你并祝你好运! - 谢谢你 长官
Dismissed.
解散
Looks like you lost another platoon leader, Web?
看来你又失去一位排长 韦伯
So, a second patrol never happened.
所以根本没有第二次巡逻
Word was Capt. Nixon wrote up a bogus report...
传说尼克森上尉写了份假报告
...and regiment never got wise.
而团部也没有察觉有异
As we pulled out of Haguenau...
当我们撤出哈根努时
...many of us in Easy Company felt that a corner had been turned...
许多Ｅ连的兄弟都觉得我们已经渡过危机
...and we all might make it home alive.
我们都有希望活着回家了
So, we'll know more as soon as we get closer to the line.
我们一接近前线就会知道更多
Before I forget...
我差点忘了...
...Col. Sink's unhappy with the appearance of your uniform.
辛克上校对你的仪容不太满意
He says it's not befitting to your rank.
他说那不符合你的官阶
Oak leaves.
橡叶徽
Congratulations, Major.
恭喜你 少校
Gentlemen, we're ready.
兄弟们 我们准备好了
I'll drive.
我来开车
- Sgt. Malarkey - Good luck, sir.
- 马拉其上士 - 祝你好运 长官
- Sgt. Martin. - Yeah, Lieutenant?
- 马丁中士 - 什么事 少尉?
- Good work. - Thank you, sir.
- 干得好! - 谢谢你 长官
- Good to have you along. - Good luck, men.
- 很高兴有你加入 - 祝你们好运
Here.
来吧
I wondered if people back home would ever know...
我怀疑远在家乡的人知不知道
...what it cost the soldiers to win this war.
士兵们赢得战争所付出的代价
In America, things were already beginning to look like peace time.
在美国 人们已经象是活在和平年代了
The standard of living was on the rise, race tracks and nightclubs were booming.
生活水平开始提升 赛车跟夜总会开始流行
You couldn't get a hotel room in Miami Beach, it was so crowded.
在迈阿密海滩订不到旅馆 因为实在是人潮汹涌
How could anyone ever know of the price paid by soldiers...
人们如何能了解士兵们...
...in terror, agony, and bloodshed...
在惊恐 痛苦与血泊中的牺性
...if they'd never been to places like Normandy...
如果他们从未身处于诺曼底...
...Bastogne, or Haguenau?
巴斯通 或是哈根努?